LOOΠΔ : Hello, we’re LOOΠΔ!!
HaSeul : Finally, our LOOΠΔ TV has reached 100th episode!
HeeJin : I’m so happy about...
HeeJin : that I’ve made a lot of good memories with members and fans together
HeeJin : while filming LOOΠΔ TV
HyunJin : I can’t believe LOOΠΔ TV has reached 100 episodes…
HyunJin : Also, I'm curious how many more episodes of LOOΠΔ TV will be produced!
HyunJin : I'm looking forward to it, too!
YeoJin : We have to do it until #1,000, #10,000~
HaSeul : (Tackle!) Really?
YeoJin : Yes!! Sure!!!
#101 starting from tomorrow
HaSeul : And ViVi’s Busan episodes will begin from #101!
HaSeul : We’ll need your support and love for upcoming ViVi’s episodes!
ViVi : I really love it~ I’m so wondering~
HaSeul : I love it, love it!
ViVi : I can’t wait!!
LOOΠΔ : Until now, we were LOOΠΔ!
HyunJin : Until #200~
HaSeul, YeoJin, ViVi : Until #300~
HaSeul : Until #1,000~
HaSeul : #200,000,000
YeoJin : #1,000,000,000,000!!